Contact

Jalandhar , Punjab das.anshuman2018@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ianshu (LinkedIn) whoisanshuman.netlify.app/ (Portfolio) www.seconset.in (Blog)

Top Skills

Ethical Hacking

Python

C++

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Professional Working)
Bengali (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Certified Ethical Hacking Professional

Ethical Hacking: Social Engineering

OWASP Top 10: #3 Sensitive Data Exposure and #4 External Entities (XXE)

Summer Training in C/CPP

Penetration Testing: Advanced Web Testing

Honors-Awards

Hall Of Fame

Hall Of Fame

Recognition for Securing India's Cyber Space

Publications

My Journey to become a Vouched Mozillian

Anshuman Das

Offensive Security Researcher
Jalandhar

Summary

Anshuman is a techgeek who is curious about various technologies and loves to explore in daily basis and concerns about Security and Privacy.

•Professionally he is a Cyber Security Researcher, Penetration tester, CTF player and an Ethical Hacker and Advocate for Privacy. He is also a Technical Content Writer love to share his knowledge through write-ups and blog.

#Python #C/C++ #Java #Bash #Operating System #Database Management #Networking #Linux #Ethical Hacking #Pentesting #CTF Technical Content Writing

✓#Wireshark ✓#BurpSuite ✓#JohnTheReapper ✓#Nmap
✓#Gobuster ✓#Nikto ✓#Metasploit ✓#Hashcat

•In spite of these he loves to do Community works whether it is building a community or serving for community:

He serves for Mozilla Community in various Privacy Campaigns.

He serves for GirlScript Foundation whose motto is to provide free and quality education to enthusiast geeks all over India.

He mentors the beginners to start their journey in Cybersecurity field. Trained more than 200+ schools & college students all over India.

He is currently leading a open Cybersecurity Community as well as platform : SecOnset (www.seconset.in)

.

- *#Speaker *#Leadership *#Teamwork *#Comunicaton
- ***#Nagotiation *#Presentation *#Team** Building ***#** Mentoring

Do You want to explore /learn /discuss related to CyberSec field/ Open-Source/Community Building then hit him up anytime

: anshuman.11701200@gmail.com(queries/discussion/suggestions)

:anshuman@seconset.in(organization related)

Experience

SecOnset

Team Lead

February 2020 - Present (7 months)

SecOnset is an E-Learning Platform as well as Blog for those(school & college students) who want to start their adventurous career journey in Cybersecurity field.

As a Platform it provides:

- Resources(Write-ups, Tutorials and ebooks etc.) for free to start journey in Cybersecurity

a lot more to come!

for more info : https://www.seconset.in

Ittoolstraining

Campus Ambassador Lead

July 2020 - Present (2 months)

Here my responsibilities are as follows:

- Managing a group of Campus Ambassadors
- Assign them their task
- Make them understand their respective tasks and help them with proper guidance to clear their doubts
- Help them to grow personally and professionally

Hack The Box

Hacker

March 2020 - Present (6 months)

Just Started exploring this platform! Enjoying the Learning while hunting down those machines!

Mozilla Punjab

11 months

Organizer

January 2020 - Present (8 months)

Core Member

October 2019 - Present (11 months)

Jalandhar Area, India

It a community mainly focusing on PRIVACY AND SECURITY of every individual. Open Source is becoming more powerful gradually as Mozilla.

Organized events:

- # Hacktoberfest 2019
- # AutumnHacks 2019
- # Common Voice for Mozilla -2019
- # Internet Health Day -2020
- # Online Meetups and Webinars

Contributions:

- # Localization for Mozilla Projects
- # Bugzilla Reporting Bug
- # Mozilla Open Design Graphics Designing.

Campaigns:

Localization Team in Privacy Month Campaign - 2020 Public Money, Public Code (ongoing)

My Journey of becoming Vouched Mozillian:

https://medium.com/mozilla-india/tour-de-force-got-my-first-vouch-proud-mozillian-cae1be94a9a7

Bugcrowd

Cyber Security Researcher March 2020 - Present (6 months)

- Web Application Bug Hunting
- 6+ Hall of Fame

TryHackMe
Pen-testers /CTF player
February 2020 - Present (7 months)

THIS IS A PLATFORM WHERE I TEST MY SKILLS IN HACKING THROUGH CTF challenges and BREKING THROUGH REAL SYSTEMS. IT PROVIDES REAL LIFE SCENARIOS.

Level 9(OMNI) in this platform!

WhiteMax Software Solution Penetration Tester May 2020 - Present (4 months) Jalandhar, Punjab

Here my responsibilities are:

- · Conduct Tests on network and web application
- · Conducts security audits
- · Analyze security policies
- · Writing Security Assessment report

IncludeHelp

1 year 3 months

Intership Coordinator October 2019 - February 2020 (5 months)

Technical Content Writer
December 2018 - February 2020 (1 year 3 months)

GirlScript Foundation Community Organizer June 2019 - February 2020 (9 months)

Jalandhar Area, India

a non-profit organization which is focusing on motivating youth in the field of various technologies. It is my pleasure working with this growing organization as a community organizer in Jalandhar chapter. Overall in India there are 36 chapters and 2 global chapters.

Organized events:

Git and GitHub - 2019

Hacktoberfest - 2019

AutumHacks - an exclusive Hackathon - 2019

GirlScript India Summit - 2019 CFP Day -2020

AppDividend
Technical Content Writer
April 2019 - July 2019 (4 months)

RiseLPU Coordinator September 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 4 months)

Education

Lovely Professional University

BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Rampurhat JL Vidyabhaban Higher Secondary, Physics Chemistry Math · (2014 - 2016)